So it was resolved overnight.
Okay.
And the tags have been shared for
deployment.
It has it kick-started or is it to be
started?
So the tags have been shared for the
deployment.
Okay.
I don't know whether it has been deployed
or not. Let me just cheque it.
If Vinod is coordinating,
can you ask Vinod to join?
Yeah.
So the tags are not deployed yet,
but it is shared with Tekion team.
But let me just ask Rowan also to join.
Sure, OK.
Does the tag have data bricks connector
settings also?
No,
so Databricks is yet to be supported in
Enterprise context graph,
but as discussed,
Mm.
we do have a support for, you know,
as an indexing as a knowledge in the
agent.
So...
Ohh, let me just, I,
I also shared my screen and...
Yeah, in the knowledge set,
in the knowledge set, it will be there,
but not as part of the context level.
No.
Up.
So, even like for the current tags also,
the Jothi will do the deployment and 1 PM
Mm.
was the time that was given.
For deployment.
Yes.
Okay, okay. Now,
will the current tag have data bricks in
the context graph or is it only for the
agent?
That's not it too.
It, for now,
Databricks is not supported in ECG,
in Enterprise context.
It is only supported in knowledge for a
nation yet to be supported.
It is it is in still development.
Okay.
So do we have any timeline on that?
Because this, as per our plan rate,
we wanted that to be deployed on 21st.
Yeah.
so that we can play out for the
connectivity and play data in this.
No.
Yeah, so...
Yes, hi Ravi. Sorry, I was late.
So the data bricks timeline that we gave
Yes.
us for development,
the 23rd is the deployment.
No.
Let me share this to you.
Yep.
So, as per this, the plan, right,
so we have told that it must be
provisioned by 21st July,
and we'll try for the ingestion rate.
Oh.
It.
No, that is why,
because we want to try for in this end,
if we face any issues on in this end,
because the first time we are trying,
that is why.
OK, the notes are slightly misleading.
Yeah, I should update this,
Oh.
but so we'll do the deployment on 23rd.
We are doing the development part from
21st.
Uh, Sricharan,
can you capture a list of items slipped
I
here? So, 20th of July,
the pre-prod deployment is not yet done.
No, can you capture it is slipped?
Yeah, thanks.
Yeah.
B.
Anything else we have produced this?
It's within guests.
Ohh, like the uh, similarly corrupting,
so then based the position that he said
he'd come back with, uh, go ahead.
Yes, so Bharathi,
we discussed with engineering regarding
Thank you.
an approach for this. So still,
we are still recommending that we use a
Right.
single common graph and regarding data
isolation so that node and assets do not
get merged between dealers.
We have come up with an approach where we
can first do an initial classification
layer.
Where we take every asset and classify it
as a dealer,
and then using that dealer tag,
we propagate that along the graph
creation.
So whenever an enrichment agent is
performing an enrichment and connecting
it to any node on the graph,
it will have that dealer tag into it and
then it will accordingly assign it.
So due to this,
none of the data gets merged along
dealers, across dealers.
OK, OK, fine. So, what we can do, right?
So, to reduce this ambiguity,
Ohh.
and so what are steps, right?
If you can share this PDF, right? So,
how do we want to start with this graph,
because we are anyway on the verge of
deployment, right? So,
next stage would be for the engineering
solution.
Right, so if you can share a draught,
it may not, it may not be perfect also,
it's OK,
but if you can share a plan on how do we
want to tackle this and how the data
addition we need to,
we can have multiplayer picture and
reduce this.
Okay,
definitely I will share that document.
Yeah.
So tomorrow's call, we can,
before tomorrow's call, if you can share,
right,
we can also have a review on that and we
can mainly discuss on the queries or any
Q&A of that.
Yes, OK.
Hold on.
Nothing from our side,
Rohan and Harshita Uriarte.
Yes,
so I had some queries about the
Databricks part. So within Databricks,
you would have a single catalogue,
and within that catalogue,
all the tables are there, right?
Or do you are you using multiple
catalogues?
Correct, please.
No, for now,
we are using only one catalogue.
One catalogue and some number of schemas,
or is that a single schema as well?
How many of you have any idea about that,
whether schema will be different or it
will be the same?
Not really sure about the underlying data
we are going to be using,
but we can assume like it can be spread
across multiple schemas.
Because when initially when I spoke with
Vijay,
he told about gold and professional
services.
I think gold is a catalogue thing.
Yes, schema is professional services.
If we are just going to be consuming that,
Up.
that's going to be just one.
OK, so I think streamers can be multiple.
Okay.
We cannot always expect it in one to be
in one screen, one screen, yeah,
all take is 10.
Yes, yes.
OK, so.
Any other queries, Varun?
No, nothing right now. Thank you, Ravi.
Yeah.
Thanks, Dean.